businesscasestudies.co.uk 2018-03-23

# Business Case Studies

The following statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you.

### 1\. Statement of intent

From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name and email address etc.) in order to receive or use services on our website. Such services include newsletters, competitions, downloads and membership. By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable Business Case Studies and its service providers to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. Our services are designed to give you the information that you want to receive. Business Case Studies will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.

### 2\. Information on visitors

During the course of any visit to Business Case Studies, the pages you see are downloaded to your computer. If you choose to login and make use of our Member tools, a cookie will be set by Business Case Studies & Facebook - Most, if not all, websites do this, because cookies allow the website publisher to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the site before. 

Cookies are completely optional on Business Case Studies and unless you login using Facebook they will not be activated, they are used only to save you having to enter your information each time you wish to access/download certain areas of the site.

### 3\. Use and storage of your personal information

When you supply any personal information to Business Case Studies (e.g. for competitions, or to download certain files) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we deal with that data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular pages that let you know why we are requesting the information). In general, any information you provide to Business Case Studies will only be used within the Business Case Studies and *MBA Publishing. It will never be supplied to anyone outside these organisations without first obtaining your consent, unless we are obliged or permitted by law to disclose it. Also, if you post or send offensive or inappropriate content anywhere on or to Business Case Studies or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on Business Case Studies, and the Business Case Studies considers such behaviour to be serious and/or repeated, Business Case Studies can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behaviour. This may include informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school or e-mail provider about the content and your behaviour.

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or, you no longer wish to continue your registration as a user. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

### 4\. Users 16 and under

If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to Business Case Studies. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information.

### Business Case Studies is produced by:

Business Case Studies LLP  
Suite 311  
Clifford House  
7-9 Clifford Street  
York  
YO1 9RA
